<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="ExtraDetailingTools" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="This mod gives you access to a bunch of useful tools and assets for detailing your city." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
# ExtraDetailingTools

### I'm recommending you to read this page on the website not in game, the game doesn't support all the formatting the web page does.

You can see the trailer video made by Sully in the "MORE ABOUT THIS MOD" section.

If you want example of builds that use this mod, you can check the about screenshots section lower in the description.

# Features:
* Transform Tool
* More Snapping Option
* NetLanes
* Surfaces
* Decals

## Transform Tool
The Transform UI appears when you select a compatible asset. This allows you to change the positioning and rotation of the object along the XYZ axis. You are also able to change the increment (↕) value. This can provide a lot more precision for positioning and rotation.

This menu also has a new 'delete' button, for all objects.

## ExtraAssetsMenu

In the games main navigation, you’ll find the ExtraAssetsMenu. In here you’ll find three different tabs:

### NetLanes
Netlanes (NetTool) use the same functionality as road networks, it can be used to create network fencing, or road markings to any length. This tool is more versatile than using prop line tool with fence props.

### Surfaces
There are many vanilla surfaces found in this tab. They are separated into categories such as ground, grass, tiles,...

### Decals
Here you’ll find vanilla decals. There are decals to place on the ground, like road markings and stains, and decals you can place on vertical walls.

## Snap to surface toggle
This is a feature found in the editor, now in game. This will allow you to place decals like graffiti and posters, on vertical walls. This can also be used to snap any object to any surface. From placing props on rooftops, right up to placing trees horizontally on walls.

You’ll find this alongside the other snapping options in the games UI.

# About the screenshots
- FewCandy's farm, you can find the full video about this build [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_Fp8JWzQXg).

# Translation
⚠️ This mod uses crowdin so there maybe inconsistencies with translations due to translations from different translators ⚠️
- ⚠️French 20%
- ⚠️Chinese Simplified 10% : RilkeXS(无手文) (RilkeXS)
- ❌Chinese Traditional 0%
- ⚠️German 41% : Konsi
- ❌Italian 0%
- ❌Japanese 0%
- ⚠️Korean 89% : Twotoolus-FLY-LShst, Hinanchovo
- ✔️Polish 100% : Lisek, karmel68
- ❌Portuguese, Brazilian 0%
- ❌Russian 0%
- ✔️Spanish 100% : Alex (AlexofCA)

# Thanking
I must particularly thank all the people who helped me in this major project which lasted several months :
* CityRat : Thanks for all you did, testing the mod since the start, without you, I wouldn't have started ELT project.
* Sully: planning, testing since ELT 3.0, promotions and your incredible build that you made with this mod, you gave me confidence in this project.
* Yenyang : Without you, this mod wouldn't exist, thank you for all.
* T. D. W. : Your help was precious, on various aspects of this mod.
* Konsi (Mimonsi/kosch104) : Testing since ELT 3.0, feedback and good idea. I'm glad to see that your mods are appreciated.
* Tigon Ologdring : Testing since ELT 3.0, feedback, and is good build idea that help to have faith in this project
* Dome : Testing since ELT 3.0, feedback, you did a great job finding how to create custom station and other stuff to link to the pathfinding.
* CanadianMoosePlays : Thanks for playing with ELT 3.0, even it never see the light at least somebody use it.
* CodiakTheKodiak : Thanks for your streams that I watched while I was coding, you are a great streamer.
* Jay : You destroyed my mod, I've never seen anyone use a mod so much, I'm glad I had you as a tester.

I have also have to thanks all the content creator who try the mod and build amazing stuff, you can find them under with the link to their channel.
- [Sully](https://www.youtube.com/@sully_skylines)
- [Biffa Plays Indie Games](https://www.youtube.com/@BiffaPlaysCitiesSkylines)
- [CanadianMoosePlays](https://www.twitch.tv/canadianmooseplays)
- [City Planner Plays](https://www.youtube.com/@CityPlannerPlays)
- [CodiakTheKodiak](https://www.twitch.tv/codiakthekodiak)
- [FewCandy](https://www.youtube.com/@fewcandy)
- [OVERCHARGED EGG](https://www.youtube.com/@OVERCHARGEDEGG)
- [Slay3K](https://www.twitch.tv/slay3k)
- [two dollars twenty](https://www.youtube.com/@twodollarstwenty)
  </LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/EDT.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
  <Dependency Id="75724" />
  <Dependency Id="75250" />
  <Dependency Id="74604" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="" />
	<!--ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog-->
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
  <ExternalLink Type="youtube" Url="https://youtu.be/aALkRFdWOhM?si=nd_caJkElHPi6thE" />
  <ExternalLink Type="crowdin" Url="https://crowdin.com/project/extradetailingtools" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/AlphaGaming7780/ExtraDetailingTools" />
	<ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/TritonSupreme" />
</Publish>
